A Guide to The Papers of Robert C. Fitzgerald, 1973-1988
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Annexation Cases
  - Berryville Area Master Plan. County of Clarke. Town of Berryville. Map. n.d., 1987-1989. (Box Oversize shelf)
- Family Savings and Loan of Virginia and Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works Inc. Files.
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - By-Laws and Articles of Incorporation 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Addendum to Employment Agreement and Grashaw Employment Contract 1978 (Box 22)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Correspondence, memoranda, reports. 1979, Jan. - Feb. 1980 (Box 22)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Correspondence; drafts of letter of intent and merger agreement; memoranda; merger agreement. 1979, Jul. - Feb. 1980 (Box 22)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Burke Lease. Copy of final lease. 1979, Oct. (Box 22)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Regulation issued by the State Corporation Commission or the Commission of Banking Pursuant to the Provisions of the Family Savings and Loan Act. 1980 (Box 23)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Loan Participation Agreement and Family Savings and Loan Agreement 1980, Mar. - Dec. (Box 23)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - Offer of Savings and Loan Association. 1981 (1971-1982) (Box 23)
  - Family Savings and Loan Association of Virginia - reports, memoranda, board of directors minutes, some correspondence. 1981, Sep. - Dec. (Box 23)
  - Fauquier County Water and sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. - Proceedings before F. C. C. 1970, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. - Appraisals and reports 1979-1980 (Box 23)
  - Fauquier Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. [Copies of] past correspondence 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
  - Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. - Correspondence 1980-1982 (Box 23)
  - Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. - Exhibits 1978-1980 (Box 24)
  - Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. - Pleadings 1979-1981 (Box 24)
  - Fauquier County Water and Sanitation Authority v. Marshall Water Works, Inc. - printed materials n. d. (Box 24)